# KRZYSZTOF JANIEC

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER



contact@kjaniec.dev

https://kjaniec.dev

https://github.com/kjaniec-dev

in https://linkedin.com/in/kjaniec-dev

## **SKILLS**

- Typescript
- Java
- Node.JS
- Spring Boot
- React
- Angular
- PostgreSQL
- Elasticsearch
- Redis
- RabbitMQ
- Docker
- Kubernetes

# **EDUCATION**

INFORMATICS, 2ND DEGREE

University of Zielona Góra 2012 - 2013

# **PROFILE**

Full-Stack Developer with over 10 years of experience analyzing, designing, and integrating front-end and backend-based applications. Proficient with various platforms, languages. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team.

## **EXPERIENCE**

### **SOFTWARE ENGINEER**

Biot Sp. z o.o.

2019 - Present

Development of URBAN IoT platform for managing city infrastructure

See <a href="https://biotcloud.com">https://biotcloud.com</a>

### **SOFTWARE DEVELOPER**

Cinkciarz.pl

2015 - 2019

- Implementing API Gateway for web and mobile
- Forex communication with broker platform, implementing back office for KYC process
- Merchants / Payment

#### **SENIOR EPR DEVELOPER**

Trax S.A. / Icomp sp. z o.o.

2012 - 2014

- Developing new business logic within the SQL and Visual Basic scripts
- Creating enhancements, add-ons, and reports, providing support